<resources>

    <!-- Preferences -->
    <string name="gdpr_preference_file">gdpr</string>
    <string name="gdpr_preference">gdpr_consent</string>

    <!-- Dialog -->
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_title">Data Protection Consent</string>
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_text">This app personalizes your advertising experience through <i>%1$s</i>. By consenting to this enhanced ad experience, you\'ll see ads that the ad providers and it\'s partners believe are more relevant to you. Depending on your privacy settings, <i>%2$s</i> and its partners may collect and process personal data such as device identifieres, location data and other demographic and interest data about you to provide this personalized advertising experience.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>By agreeing, you are confirming that you are over the age of 16 and would like a personalized ad experience.</string>

    <string name="gdpr_dialog_text_after_accepted_personal">Great. We hope you enjoy your personalized ad experience, but if you ever change your mind, you can withdraw your consent in the app settings at any time.</string>
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_text_after_accepted_non_personal">No problem. <i>%1$s</i> and it\'s partners won\'t collect your data through this app for personalized advertising. If you ever change your mind, you can withdraw your consent in the app settings at any time.</string>
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_text_after_no_ads_accepted">Sadly you do not want to support us by showing ads. If you ever change your mind, you can reset this decision in the app settings at any time.</string>

    <string name="gdpr_dialog_agree">Yes, I agree</string>
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_disagree">No, thank you</string>
    <string name="gdpr_dialog_close">Close</string>

    <string name="gdpr_dialog_disagree_no_ads">No ads at all, please</string>

    <string name="gdpr_dialog_disagree_info">I understand that I still see ads, but they may not be as relevant to my interests.</string>

    <!-- Ad Networks -->
    <string name="gdpr_network_admob">AdMob</string>
    <string name="gdpr_network_admob_link">https://www.google.com/admob/</string>

</resources>
